{
    "id": "ace9edfba2a8464da5e4d29a92c29587",
    "title": "Identify The Tense",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He walked out of the room without looking at anybody.",
            "description": "We make the simple past with the second form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "simple present",
                "simple past",
                "past perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is crying at the top of his voice.",
            "description": "We make the present continuous tense with be + ing form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "simple past",
                "present continuous",
                "present perfect continuous"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Small men never did great deeds.",
            "description": "We make the simple past with the second form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "simple present",
                "simple past",
                "past perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will never have betrayed my country.",
            "description": "We make the future perfect tense form with will have + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "present perfect",
                "past perfect",
                "future perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "John has broken his leg.",
            "description": "The present perfect tense form is made with has / have + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "simple present",
                "present perfect",
                "simple future"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We need air and water to survive.",
            "description": "We make the simple present tense with the first form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "simple present",
                "simple past",
                "present perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This has been going on for a while.",
            "description": "We make the present perfect continuous tense with has/have + been + ing form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "present continuous",
                "present perfect continuous",
                "past perfect continuous"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The child was sleeping in his room.",
            "description": "We use the past continuous tense with was/were + ing form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "simple past",
                "past continuous",
                "past perfect continuous"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They had already left.",
            "description": "The past perfect tense form is made with had + past participle form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "simple past",
                "present perfect",
                "past perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They had been waiting for hours.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "past perfect",
                "past perfect continuous",
                "simple past"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She will arrive soon.",
            "description": "We make the simple future tense forms with will / shall + first form of the verb.",
            "answers": [
                "simple future",
                "future continuous",
                "future perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They will be having dinner.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "simple future",
                "future continuous",
                "future perfect"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}